A Guide to the 2300 Club, Records, 1965-2000
Library of Virginia
Library of Virginia
2300 Club, Records, 1965-2000
Library of Virginia
36895, 37702
.9 cubic feet; 2 boxes; box numbers 1-2
2300 Club, Richmond, Virginia.
Administrative Information
Access Restrictions
Open only to Club Manager, President and other officers in exercise of their duties; others need written permission from President and Board of Directors.
Acquisition Information
Gift of 2300 Club, P. O. Box 7922, Richmond, Virginia 23223, 18 October 1999 and 16 October 2000
Historical Information
Founded in March 1964 as a not-for-profit social club, the 2300 Club, located in Historic Church Hill of Richmond, is a private dinner and luncheon club for residents of Church Hill and Richmond interested in the historic preservation of the area.
Scope and Content Information
Records, 1965-2000 [ongoing], (bulk 1995-2000), including agendas, annual reports, balance sheets, budget proposals, bylaws, committee reports, correspondence, house rules, lists, membership rosters, menus, and minutes relating to the operation and history of the 2300 Club. Also, includes legal records relating to the Club's problems with the IRS concerning unpaid taxes for 1990 and 1991. Arranged in the following series: I. Board of Directors; II. History; III. Legal Records; IV. General Membership Annual Meetings. The minutes for a particular meeting are located with the agenda of the next meeting.
Arrangement
Files arranged chronologically.
Contents List
- Board of Directors (Box 1-2)
  - Strategic Planning Committee Report, February 1996 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - September 1996-January 2000 (Box 1, Folder 2-34)
  - February 2000-October 2000 (Box 2, Folder 1-9)
  - Board of Directors Retreat, February 1999 (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Board of Directors Membership Roster, November 1999 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- History (Box 2)
  - History and Archives Committee Annual Report, 1997-1998 (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - 2300 Club Presidents (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - The 2300 Club Membership Roster, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Annual Reports filed with the State Corporation Commission, 1965-1998 (Box 2, Folder 15-16)
  - Plantings in the Garden at the 2300 Club, October 1984 (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Questions re. public use of the club, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 18)
  - Bylaws and House Rules (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Legal Records (Box 2)
  - Legal Records, December 1995-April 1997 (Box 2, Folder 20-23)
- General Membership Annual Meetings, 1998-1999 (Box 2)
  - General Membership Annual Meeting, October 1998 (Box 2, Folder 24)
  - General Membership Annual Meeting, October 1999 (Box 2, Folder 25)